<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About me on Introduction</title>
    <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About me on Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Employments &amp; Education</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/cvw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/cvw/</guid>
      <description>Here I give you a brief overview of my previous employment and training.
Employments 02/2023 - 09/2024 Researcher (EU-Horizon project G-EPIC), Chair of Methods in Political Science, Justus Liebig University Giessen - during this, guest stay at Universidad Carlos III de Madrid (2 weeks) and six-months at the Universidade Federal de Pernambuco (Recife, Brazil)
- planning, managing and conducting statistical analyses (with R, Python, and SQL)
- preparing &amp;amp; publishing reports &amp;amp; academic papers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/teaching/</guid>
      <description>As a research assistant at the Chair of Methods in Political Science, I have continuously taught in the Institute&amp;rsquo;s degree programs, focusing on the practical teaching of empirical social research in the BA program in Social Sciences.
My interest in education is reflected in my experience training and supervising students (e.g., on final-year projects). My teaching roles have equipped me to impart knowledge successfully, prepare and present complex content effectively, guide discussions, and provide constructive feedback to facilitate learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/research/</guid>
      <description>My research interests lie in political socialization and political attitude/support research. Below, you will find an overview of the research projects.
In smaller and more extensive research projects, I developed my skills in planning and organizing projects and discovering and consolidating my strength in team collaboration. In addition, I steadily expanded my skills in the application and evaluation of quantitative data analysis.
One of my strengths lies in understanding large amounts of information, a crucial skill in my research endeavors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Additional training</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/training/</guid>
      <description>Methods 2024: Oxford Spring School: Machine Learning with R 2023: Gesis Spring Seminar: Comparative Social Research with Multi-Group SEM 2021: ECPR Virtual Spring School in Methods and Techniques 2021, KU Leuven: Introduction to Structural Equation Modelling 2020: ECPR Virtual Summer School in Methods and Techniques 2020, CEU Budapest: Quantitative Text Analysis 2019: 48. Gesis Spring Seminar “Bayesian Modelling in the Social Sciences: Introduction to Bayesian Models for the Social Sciences 2018: ECPR Summer School in Methods and Techniques 2018, CEU Budapest: Applied Multilevel Regression Modelling 2016: 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Look</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/overview/</guid>
      <description>Here you find a quick overview of important areas of my professional career. You can find a more comprehensive overview in my academic CV: EN, PT, DE.
During my academic activities, I have given international scientific presentations, as well as public lectures in which I presented scientific content/problems to a wider audience. Furthermore, I published part of my work internationaly. In particular, I expanded my interpersonal and cultural skills at conferences and stays abroad.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
