<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About me on Introduction</title>
    <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About me on Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Education &amp; Jobs</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/cvw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/cvw/</guid>
      <description>Here I give you a brief overview of my previous employment and training.
Employments 02/2023 - 09/2024 Researcher (international research project G-EPIC), Chair of Methods in Political Science, Justus Liebig University Giessen - during this, guest stay at Universidad Carlos III de Madrid (2 weeks) and six-months at the Universidade Federal de Pernambuco (Recife, Brazil) 10/2015 - 09/2022 Research assistant (for doctoral studies), Chair of Methods in Political Science, Justus Liebig University Giessen</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching Projects</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/teaching/</guid>
      <description>As a research assistant at the Chair of Methods in Political Science, I have continuously taught in the Institute&amp;rsquo;s degree programs, focusing on the practical teaching of empirical social research in the BA program in Social Sciences.
My interest in education is reflected in my experience training and supervising students (e.g., on final-year projects). My teaching roles have equipped me to impart knowledge effectively, prepare and present complex content effectively, guide discussion, and provide constructive feedback to facilitate learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Projects</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/research/</guid>
      <description>In my work life so far, I have worked as a research assistant in teaching. During this time, I have also been involved in research projects temporarily. I am working on the EU Horizon project G-EPIC until September 2024.
In these research projects, I developed my skills in planning and organizing projects and discovered and consolidated my strength in team collaboration. In addition, I continuously expanded my skills in applying and evaluating quantitative data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Additional training</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/training/</guid>
      <description>Methods training 2023: Gesis Spring Seminar: Comparative Social Research with Multi-Group SEM 2021: ECPR Virtual Spring School in Methods and Techniques 2021, KU Leuven: Introduction to Structural Equation Modelling 2020: ECPR Virtual Summer School in Methods and Techniques 2020, CEU Budapest: Quantitative Text Analysis 2019: 48. Gesis Spring Seminar “Bayesian Modelling in the Social Sciences: Introduction to Bayesian Models for the Social Sciences 2018: ECPR Summer School in Methods and Techniques 2018, CEU Budapest: Applied Multilevel Regression Modelling 2016: 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academia</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/academics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/academics/</guid>
      <description>During my academic activities, I have given international scientific presentations and publications, as well as public lectures in which I presented scientific content/problems to a wider audience. In particular, I expanded my interpersonal and cultural skills at conferences and stays abroad.
At the Chair of Methods in Political Science, I was involved to a large extent in the organization of the professorship and the coordination of student assistants.
Stays abroad 2023 Universidade Federal de Pernambuco (Recife), Research stay, 6 monthsUniversidad Carlos III de Madrid, Research stay, 2 weeks Conferences 2023 IPSA World CongressP, ECPR General ConferenceC, P 2022 DVPW Arbeitskreis HochschullehreP, DVPW Sektion Politikwissenschaft und Politische BildungP 2021 Learning schools for democracy?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
