<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Research on Introduction</title>
    <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Research on Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/publications/</guid>
      <description>Peer-reviewed Journals Hunklinger, M., &amp;amp; Kleer, P. (forthcoming). Why do LGB vote left? Insight into left-wing voting of lesbian, gay and bisexual citizens in Austria. Electoral Studies.
Abendschön, S., Kleer, P., &amp;amp; Faas, T. (2022). Out-of-school learning as an effective tool of civic education in elementary school? Evidence from germany. Citizenship, Social and Economic Education, 21, 153–171. https://doi.org/10.1177/14788047221120682
Contributions in Edited Books Abendschön, S., &amp;amp; Kleer, P. (2023). Politische Informationskompetenz online.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conferences/Talks</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/konferenzen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/konferenzen/</guid>
      <description>Conferences 2023 IPSA World CongressP, ECPR General ConferenceC, P 2022 DVPW Arbeitskreis HochschullehreP, DVPW Sektion Politikwissenschaft und Politische BildungP 2021 Learning schools for democracy? Young People, Politics and Civic Education (VU Brüssel/UL Brüssel)P 2019 ECPR General ConferenceP, Joint International Teaching and Learning Conference (PSA, ECPR, BISA, APSA)P 2018 Tagung der Jungen Osteuropa-ExpertInnen (DGO)P, 3. Ostasiatische DAAD-ZentrenkonferenzP, EUSA Asia PacificP 2017 2. Ostasiatische DAAD-ZentrenkonferenzP Invited Talks 2023 Finding the gap: gender differences in political engagement (Lecture Series, University of Roehampton) Using continuous integration in teaching (HackyHour Gießen) 2019 Das Web-Based-Training in der Praxis: Erfahrungen aus der Anwendung im Studienbeginn (Master) (Digitale Hochschullehre in den Geistes- und Kulturwissenschaften, Justus-Liebig-Universität Gießen) 2018 Kinder im Landtag: nachhaltige Lernerlebnisse von Grundschulkindern (Ringvorlesung, Institut für Politikwissenschaft, Justus-Liebig-Universität Gießen) Sind die demokratischen Systeme in Ostmitteleuropa in der Krise?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/diss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/diss/</guid>
      <description>Fundamental Conditions of Democracy: Inequality as Disturbing Factor of Democratic Consolidation (dissertation project) Duration: 02/2016 until 12/2022 In the 1990s and early 2000s, the economic shock in Central Eastern Europe (CEE) after the transformation was still tolerated, but with accession to the EU, it became clear that the expected level of prosperity would not be achieved for a long time. Nevertheless, the political systems of CEE could be considered consolidated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>G-EPIC (projekt work)</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/gepic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/gepic/</guid>
      <description>Gender Empowerment Through Politics in the Classroom 02/2023 - 01/2026, PI (Germany): Simone Abendschön Project staff (Germany): B. Philipp Kleer, Tim Schmidt Funded by: EU Horizon G-EPIC aims to tackle the challenge of gendered political inequality from an intersectional perspective, through a novel research programme that broadly assesses how the gender gap in political participation is learnt through interaction in a social educational context. It proposes to develop a systematic approach, to gain understanding of the state of play on gendered political inequality and then to design, pilot and evaluate inclusive school-based interventions (didactics) that foster the political self-efficacy of disadvantaged young girls in six European countries (Belgium, Czechia, Denmark, Germany, Spain and the United Kingdom).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Methods training</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/training/</guid>
      <description>03/2023: Gesis Spring Seminar: Comparative Social Research with Multi-Group SEM 03/2021: ECPR Virtual Spring School in Methods and Techniques 2021, KU Leuven: Introduction to Structural Equation Modelling 08/2020: ECPR Virtual Summer School in Methods and Techniques 2020, CEU Budapest: Quantitative Text Analysis 03/2019: 48. Gesis Spring Seminar &amp;ldquo;Bayesian Modelling in the Social Sciences: Introduction to Bayesian Models for the Social Sciences 07/2018: ECPR Summer School in Methods and Techniques 2018, CEU Budapest: Applied Multilevel Regression Modelling 08/2016: 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kinder im Landtag (projekt work)</title>
      <link>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/kil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bpkleer.de/en/projects/kil/</guid>
      <description>Children in a German State Parliament: Lasting Learning Experiences of Primary Schoolchildren 12/2017 - 08/2018 Project heads: Simone Abendschön, Thorsten Faas Project staff: B. Philipp Kleer, Luisa Wingerter Funded by: State Parliament Rhineland-Palatinate The state parliament (Landtag) of the Bundesland Rhineland-Palatinate developed an out-of-school political education program in 2018, taking place in the Landtag itself. This new visiting program aimed exclusively at primary schoolchildren in grades 3 and 4. The program aimed at strengthening political knowledge and democratic understanding of children, especially with reference to the political context of the German federal Land.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
